声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：Requiem校对扣扣
后期：阿胜 双语制作：sealovemoon
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
迷失 前情提要
Previously on Lost
-你没有告诉我你的处境  -我的处境压根不是问题
-You didn't tell us your condition. -My condition is not an issue.
我这样生活了四年了
I've lived with it for four years.
我会付钱让你飞回悉尼的
I'll get you on a plane back to Sydney.
我不想回悉尼去
I don't want to go back to Sydney!
你不知道你现在在和谁说话
You don't know who you're dealing with.
永远别跟我说有什么我做不到的...永远
Don't tell me what I can't do!
这是命运 这就是我的命运
This is destiny.This is my destiny!
这是...我应该做到的 混蛋
I'm supposed to do this, damn it!
你如何打开舱门?
How do you open a hatch that has no handle, no latch,
没有把手和销子的舱门
no discernible way of opening it?
那是什么?
What's that?
一个游戏
A game.
这是我最喜欢的游戏 我经常和我的兄弟一起玩
My favorite game.I used to play with my brother.
这游戏叫做老鼠陷阱
It's called Mouse Trap.
怎么玩?
How do you play?
起初 你拥有零散的全部零件
You start with all these parts off the board.
然后 一步一步的来设置陷阱
And then, one by one,you build the trap.
鞋子 桶子 盆子 一块连着一块 拼起来
Shoe. Bucket. Tub.Piece by piece,it all comes together.
然后你等着你的对手跑到这个干酪圈里
And then you wait till your opponent lands here on the old Cheese Wheel.
如果你拼接合适的话 你就能触发机关陷阱了
Then if you set it up just right,you spring the trap.
你来吧 小兄弟
Go ahead, kiddo.
夫人 我能帮你做什么不?
May I help you, ma'am?
好的
Yes...
你能告诉我橄榄球在哪儿么?
Could you tell me where the footballs are?
标准橄榄球在8号走廊 冲撞球在15号
Yeah. Aisle eight for regulation.Aisle fifteen for Nerf.
好的 谢谢 很感谢
Oh, yes, thank you. Thanks.
我说 根本就没法打开这个舱门
You want my opinion?
Boone 你应该有点信心
Boone you gotta have some faith.
我们得做的就是打破玻璃 然后再进去
All we gotta do is break the glass,and then we're in.
投石器能提供半吨重的力量
Trebuchet delivers half a ton of force.
为什么大家叫它投石器? 它更像一个弹弓
Why is it a trebuchet? Looks like a catapult.
它就叫投石器的原因是 因为它就是投石器
It's called a trebuchet,because it's a trebuchet.
我不懂 伙计
I don't get you, man.
一会儿你像个文学家似的引用尼采的话 一会儿你又成了一个工程师
One minute you're quoting Nietzsche,now you're an engineer.
我认为我不能拼出"trebuchet(投石器)"
I don't think I can spell "trebuchet."
是"T"结尾的
There's a "T" on the end.
John 我说正经的
I'm serious. John
我们两周来天天来这儿
We've been coming here every day for two weeks
你从不说说你自己
You never talk about yourself.
每个人都有他的故事
Everybody's got a story.
我的故事会让你厌烦
My story would bore you.
三  二  一
Three. Two. One.
应该能行的
This was supposed to work.
This was supposed to work!
John
你的腿 伙计
Your leg, man.
还好吧?
You OK?
没事
Yeah.
我很好
I'm fine.
你的投石器...
Your trebuchet.
为什么没起作用?
Why didn't it work?
因为它还不够结实
It didn't work because it wasn't strong enough.
我认为那玻璃破不了
That won't break,whatever it's made of.
如果加上足够的力量 任何东西都能破坏
Everything breaks if you apply the right force.
那么我们要造另一个你的发明并且希望这次能成功?
We'll build another invention and hope it works?
如果又没用呢?
What if it doesn't?
那么这小岛会告诉我们怎么做的
The island will tell us what to do.
我们应该回去那儿 抢救那些碎片
We should get back there. Salvage those pieces.
你的腿还好吧?
Your leg OK?
没事
It's fine.
你没事吧 伙计?
You all right, guy?
-你为什么跟着我?  -很抱歉
-You following me?  -I'm sorry.
-你是谁?  -我是你母亲
-Who are you?  -I'm your mother.
听着 夫人...我不知道为什么你认为我是你儿子
Look, Ms...I don't know why you think I'm your son
或是你怎么找到我的 但是...
Or how you found me, but...
你是被收养的 不是么?
You're adopted, aren't you?
不 我是在一个孤儿院长大的
No, I was raised in a foster home.
确切的说是一些孤儿院
Well, several foster homes, actually.
瞧 我不愿意无礼
Look, I don't mean to be rude.
你要从我这儿得到什么?
What do you want from me?
我想告诉你 你很特别...非常特别
I want to tell you that you're special.Very special.
你是一个计划的一部分
You are part of a design.
你已经意识到了 是么?
You do realize that, don't you?
我们的会面...我找到你...
That our meeting,me finding you,
这预示着一件事的发生...
this is a sign of things to come.
大事
Great things.
我的父亲...
My father...
他还活着么?
...is he still alive?
还活着?
Still alive?
John  你还不知道么?
Oh, John don't you understand?
你没有父亲
You don't have a father.
你是一个完美的设想
You were immaculately conceived.
哪一个?
Which one?
那个
That one.
你确定? 这个就是我在用的 但是什么都没发生
You're sure? This is the one I've been using, and nothing's happening.
那没用我很抱歉
I'm sorry it's not helping.
什么东西没用?
What's not helping?
没什么
Nothing.
还是谢谢你
Thanks anyway.
漂亮的花园
Nice garden.
怎么了?
What was that all about?
他头痛
He has headaches.
那家伙不是藏着一大箱阿司匹林么?
Doesn't the guy have aspirin stashed away somewhere?
他说阿司匹林没用
He says aspirin didn't help.
能问你个问题不?
Can I ask you a question?
听说你每天头都痛得厉害
Say you're having bad headaches.Every day.
-你没事吧?  -是的 没事
-You OK?  -Yeah. I'm fine.
那么凯特 我们谈论的人是谁呢?
So, who are we talking about then, Kate?
-Kate  -怎么
-Kate.  -Uh-huh.
我只是认为他有很大的麻烦
There might be something wrong with him.
那他怎么认为?
What does he think?
-他说他很好 但是...  -那么他就是很好
-Says he's fine...  -Then he's fine.
他能继续下去 可能会有...
He could be playing it down. There could be something...
听着 我找到一个人然后确信他没事就再好不过了
I'd love to check the guy out and make sure he's OK,
但是我们都知道唯一能使我从麻烦中解脱的 就是一句爽快地俏皮话
but we both know all I'm gonna get for my trouble is a snappy one-liner,
并且如果我真的很幸运 可能就可以有一个崭新的绰号了
and if I'm real lucky,a brand-new nickname.
那个我很在行
I'm just over it.
你迟到了
You're late.
什么迟到了?
Late for what?
工作迟到了
Late for work.
我认为我已经完成工作了 John
I think I'm done working John.
抱歉 什么?
I'm sorry. What?
这根本没用
This is useless.
你打不开那个东西
You can't open that thing up.
别跟我说有什么我做不到的
Don't tell me what I can't do.
你还不懂么? 不可能的 你不可能进去的
You get it?It's a dead end.You're not getting in.
那不可能 我们不是偶然发现这个的
We didn't find this by accident.
-我们应该可以...  -哦 我们应该可以的 是不?
-We're supposed...  -We're supposed to find this,Right?
我们能行的 是不?
We're supposed to open it,right?
我们做得到的 是不?
We're supposed to open it,Right?
那么告诉我 John
Then tell me something John.
如果我们应该可以打开它的 那么我们为什么到现在还没打开呢?
If we're supposed to open it,why haven't we opened it yet?
这岛会给我们提示的
The island will send us a sign.
"这岛会的..."
"The island will..."
所有现在发生的一切是在考验我们信念 和我们的承诺
All that's happening now is our faith is being tested.
但是我们会打开的 这个岛会告诉我们方法的
We will open it.The island will show us how.
这岛会给我们哪种提示?
What kind of sign will the island send us?
看到那个了么?
Did you see that?
Boone?
Theresa 从楼梯上掉下来了
Theresa falls up the stairs.
Theresa falls down the stairs.
Theresa 从楼梯上掉下来了
Theresa falls up the stairs.
Theresa falls down the stairs.
Theresa 从楼梯上掉下来了
-别  -Theresa 从楼梯上掉下来了
-Please don't.  -Theresa falls up the stairs.
别想起来
Don't take it back.
Boone 醒醒
Boone. Wake up.
-才几点啊?  -早上了 来吧
-What time is it?  -It's morning. Come on.
好了 好了 起来 起来 起来了
OK. I'm up.
怎么了?
What's going on?
来吧 我们走
Come on. Let's go.
Emily Annabeth Locke 一言难尽
Emily Annabeth Locke,in ten thousand words or less.
那么 她是我母亲
So, she's my mother.
我从她的车里拿到了一些头发 和你的DNA相符
I lifted some hairs from her car and matched them with your DNA.
99%确定了
It's 99 percent certain.
她被看押过几次
She was institutionalized.A few times.
不是因为犯罪或是暴力
Nothing criminal or violent.
是一种精神分裂症
It's a type of schizophrenia.
显然 如果她意识清楚地话 她是没事的
If she stays on her meds, she's OK.
我的父亲呢?
What about my father?
这是个问题
Here's the thing.
你母亲把你丢了 那你可以去质问她
Your mother sought you out, so she's fair game.
但是这个人
But this guy,
可能他根本不知道有你这个人
maybe he doesn't even know you exist.
我用了足够的时间来了解...
Now, I've done this enough times to know...
这件事并不是有意而为的 可能它让人以为是那样
...this stuff isn't meant to be,even though it may feel that way.
瞧 将来可能不会有个圆满的结局
Look, this probably won't have a happy ending.
那么...
So...
你要知道么?
...do you want it or not?
我要
I want it.
-你的名字?  -John John Locke
-Your name is? -John John Locke.
我是Anthony Cooper的儿子
I'm Anthony Cooper's son.
Cooper先生没有儿子
Mr. Cooper doesn't have a son.
告诉他我什么都不想要
Tell him I don't want anything.
我的母亲是Emily Locke 麻烦你了
My mother is Emily Locke.Please.
等一下
Just a minute.
Cooper先生 是John·Cooper 他说他是您儿子
Mr. Cooper, I got John Locke here,says he's your son.
好的 先生
Yes, sir.
你可以进去了先生
Well, you can go on in, sir.
多少有点尴尬
This is awkward.
谢谢您接见我 先生 我是...John
Thank you for seeing me, sir.I'm... John.
也许我们得为这个庆祝一下
Something tells me I'm gonna want a drink for this?
-要点喝的么?  -恩 好阿
-You want a drink? -Yeah. All right. Great.
-苏格兰的 行么?  -哦 那...谢谢了
-Scotch OK? -Yeah, that's... Thanks.
-那么 是谁找到谁的?  -抱歉 先生?
-So who found who? -I'm sorry, sir?
艾米莉 你母亲
Emily. Your mother.
是她找到你的 还是你找到她的?
Did she find you,or did you find her?
是她找到我的
She found me.
她看起来怎样?
How did she look?
我看很好
All right, I guess.
她有说我什么没?
She say anything about me?
她说我没有父亲
She said I didn't have a father.
我是一个完美的设想
That I was immaculately conceived.
真的?
Really?
我想那样我就成了上帝了?
Well, I guess that makes me God, huh?
你生下来一年后我才知道有你
I didn't know you existed until a year after you were born.
她说她甚至不想要这个孩子 不想把你生下来
She told me she wasn't gonna have the baby, you, at all.
然后她就消失了
She drops off the face of the planet.
当她再次出现时 她问我要钱
She turns up asking for money,
她说她让别人收养了你
telling me she put you up for adoption.
你喝这个 还是要其它的?
You gonna drink that or what?
你有你自己的家么?
You have a family of your own?
没有 先生
No, sir.
我也没有
Me neither.
我试过几次 但没有用
I tried it a couple times.Didn't take.
-你打猎么?  -不打
-Do you hunt? -No.
你不是做动物权利保护工作的吧 是么?
You're not an animal rights nut-job?
没有了
No, sir.
这周日你有事没?
What are you doing this Sunday?
没有
Nothing.
打猎去如何?
You wanna go hunting?
好嘛...一起去
Uh... Well, I'd like that.
是的 我很想去
Yeah, I'd like that very much.
我昨晚做了个梦
I had a dream last night.
我要一个提示
I asked for a sign.
然后我看见一架飞机坠落在了...那儿的一个海滩上
And then I saw a plane crash.A Beechcraft.Right out there.
那是一个梦
It was a dream, but...
但是这是我所经历的最真实的事了
...it was the most real thing I've ever experienced.
我知道现在该去哪儿了
I know where to go now.
去干吗?
Go for what?
去找打开这混蛋舱门的东西
To find what we need to open this bastard up.
你用这种古怪的手法想让我看到我的姐妹被吃了么?
You using that paste that made me see my sister get eaten?
不 Boone 不是
No, Boone, no.
John 我要告诉你 提示和梦还有...
Cause, I gotta tell you,signs and dreams and...
Theresa是谁?
Who's Theresa?
什么?
What?
"Theresa从楼梯上掉下来了 Theresa从楼梯上掉下来了"
"Theresa falls up the stairs.Theresa falls down the stairs."
在梦里你是这么说的
You were saying that in the dream.
你是怎么知道那个的?
How would you know about that?
我不知道 Boone 但是我们应该可以去那儿的
I don't know,but we're supposed to go to this place.
我们应该可以找到那架飞机的
We're supposed to find that plane.
你要和我来不?
Will you come with me?
我本来想问进展的怎样了
I was gonna ask you how this was going,
现在看来确实进展很快
but it's coming together fast.
那场火灾没有损失所有的东西
Fire wasn't a total loss.
我们从第一个建造的那里学到了些东西
We learned things from building the first one,
这让我们避免了反复试验和重复错误
which is saving us from trial and error.
现在的是...
Now it's just...
试验
trial.
好的 好的 好的 好的
Yeah, yeah.
是的 伙计 我知道 可以可以可以了
Yeah, man, I know."Now, now."
熟悉了一点韩语了是么?
Picking up a little Korean?
是的 现在我知道怎么说"快点"还有"白痴"
Yeah. I'm pretty sure I know how to say "faster" and "idiot".
我听说你的头有点问题
I hear you're having trouble with your head.
现在她调用你来问我了么?
Now she got you making house calls?
你也对光很敏感 是么?
You're sensitive to the light too?
我对你很敏感...
I'm sensitive to you...
好的 再见
All right.We'll see you.
医生
Doc!
对光敏感...问题严重么?
Sensitivity to the light,that bad?
看情况了
Depends.
看什么情况?
On what?
看是什么引起你的头痛了
On what's causing your headaches.
是瘤或是什么的
It's not like it's a tumor or something.
什么使你认为是个瘤?
What makes you think it's a tumor?
-我没认为  -很好 那么好的
-I don't.Great.  -OK then.
我的叔叔
My uncle...
他  患脑瘤死了
he, uh......died of a brain tumor.
是么?
Yeah?
肿瘤会不会遗传的?
That run in the family? Tumors?
是什么样的瘤?
What type of tumor was it?
可以杀死你的那种
The type that kills you.
你不觉得很有趣么?
Do you smell anything funny?
脑瘤让人产生幻觉...比方说像是什么烧起来了
Brain tumors bring on phantom smells.Maybe like something burning.
只是头痛
Just headaches.
那我想你没事
Well, I'm sure you're fine, then.
听着 如果这让你很担心 我能给你做下测试
If this is worrying you,there's tests I could do.
抱歉 医生
Sorry, doc.
听起来很有趣
Sounds fun, but...
但是我的保险过期了
my insurance ran out.
保险过期了
Insurance ran out.
很好笑的笑话
That's a good one.
我可能某天在舱口说起了她的名字
I could've mentioned her name out by the hatch one day.
-谁?  -Theresa.
-Who?  -Theresa.
可能是我的自言自语
Maybe I was talking to myself.
可能是吧
Maybe.
但是你没有
But you didn't.
那么在梦里你看见飞机坠毁 是么?
So, in this dream you saw a plane crash, right?
是的
Yeah.
好的 我们都经历过坠机的事实
OK.The fact that we were just in a plane crash,
你有没稍微想想...
you didn't think for one second...
John 你没事吧?
John, you OK?
我很好
I'm fine.
你的腿怎么了?
What is wrong with your leg?
我没事
I'm fine.
什么?
What?
有人从营地远远地到这儿来?
Someone from camp hiked all the way out here?
你觉得这是从哪儿来的?
Where do you think it came from?
他
Him.
-早上好 Eddie  -Locke先生 早上好
-Morning, Eddie. -Morning, Mr. Locke.
你们要去抓几只鸟么?
You gonna get birds again?
我希望这样
I hope so.
Anthony?
你应该12点再来
You weren't supposed to be here till 12:00.
我以为是11点
I thought you said 11:00.
这是什么?
What is this?
这是透析仪
It's a dialysis machine.
我的肾不行了
My kidney's failing.
混蛋的医生说我需要移植
Damn doctors say I need a transplant.
什么时候?
When?
明天 如果适合我的话
Tomorrow, if it were up to me.
我在捐赠人的名单上
I'm on the donor list.
但是我是个老人 那名单又很长
But I'm an old man,and it's a long list.
John 透析仪过会儿就好了
The dialysis will be fine for awhile.
我不会告诉你明确的原因的
I didn't tell you for this exact reason.
我不想让这些扰了这么美好的一天 你也不能
I'm not gonna let this spoil a fantastic day, and neither should you.
所以 这儿完成了后 我们吃顿好的午饭然后去打鸟
I'll get done here,and we'll have a nice lunch and go shoot some birds.
他是个牧师
He was a priest.
你认为他死了多久了?
How long you think he's been dead?
一般来说 两年内布料就会分解
Clothing would decompose within two years,
但 这是高质量的合成纤维
but this is high-quality polyester.
可能是两年 也可能是十年
Could be two years, could be ten.
金牙齿...明显很富裕
Gold teeth. Obviously well-off.
这是什么钱?
What kind of money is that?
尼日利亚 奈拉币
Nigerian naira.
一个尼日利亚的牧师在南太平洋的一个岛上做什么?
What is a Nigerian priest doing on an island in the South Pacific?
我不认为他是个牧师
I'm not so sure he was a priest.
能安静点么?
You wanna keep it down?
好了 起来吧
That's it. Get up.
-什么?  -起来吧
-What? -Get up.
你要去Jack那儿
You're going to Jack.
我有棒棒糖拿么?
Do I get a lollipop?
头痛是什么时候开始的?
When did the headaches start?
几天前 可能是一周
A few days ago. A week maybe.
你得呆在这儿么?
Do you have to be here?
早上起来时也痛么?
Do you have them when you wake up?
通常是在中午他们吵我的时候
Usually they hit me middle of the day.
你用那该死的东西干嘛?
What are you doing with that?
看看你的瞳孔对变化的事物的反映
Checking how your pupils respond to changing stimuli.
点头是什么意思?
What's that? That nod.
你能让他干他的么?
Let him do his thing.
我让他去了 但是我想知道他到底怎么认为...
I am, but I wanna know-What he thinks I should...
我认为你应该闭嘴然后休息一下
Shut up and relax.
你该死的在干嘛?
What are you doing?
你输过血么?
You ever had a blood transfusion?
什么? 没有
What? No.
吃过疟疾的药么?
Taken pills for malaria?
和妓女有过性行为么?
Have you ever had sex with a prostitute?
和这些事情到底有什么关系?
What's that got to do with anything?
就是说有了?
Is that a yes?
是的
Yes.
你以往感染过性病?
And have you ever contracted a sexually transmitted disease?
那也是有了
I'm gonna take that as another yes.
最后一次什么时候发作的?
When was the last outbreak?
去死吧 医生
Go to hell, doc.
-我知道是他应得的 但是...  -视力问题而已
-I know he deserved it, but... -He needs glasses.
怎么了 John?
What's going on?
没什么
Nothing.
你走得很勉强 伙计
You can barely walk, man.
是弹片留下的伤口
It's the wound from the shrapnel.
是右脚 John
That's your right leg.
左脚怎么了?
What's with your left?
我很好 别问了 混蛋
I'm fine. Now stop asking.
好了 我们回去吧
That's it. Let's go back.
不 你不好 让我带你回Jack那儿
No, you're not.Let me get you to Jack.
不 Jack不会知道起先我是怎么了
No. Jack wouldn't know the first thing about what's wrong with me.
John
-我们得...  -不 不
-We've gotta go back. -No.
你怎么了 疯了?
What is wrong with you? Are you crazy?
-我座在轮椅里  -什么?
-I was in a wheelchair.  -What?
我瘫痪了四年
Paralyzed. For four years.
飞机 我们的飞机
The plane, our plane,
起飞时我座在轮椅里 但是坠落后就没了
I was in that chair when we took off,but not after we crashed.
-你为什么会在轮椅里?  -这不重要了
-Why were you in a wheelchair?  -That doesn't matter anymore.
但是这个岛... 它改变了我 它使我更充实了
But this island,it changed me.It made me whole.
现在它想要回去了 我不知为什么
Now it's trying to take it back,and I don't know why.
但是它想让我跟着我所看见的
But it wants me to follow what I saw.
什么?
What?
四周前  我也不相信我自己
Four weeks ago,I wouldn't have believed it.
但是你和我在这儿是有原因的
We are here for a reason.
我们注定要找到一些东西...
There's something that we were meant to find.
一些能帮助我们进入舱门的东西
something that's gonna help us get into the hatch.
我知道
I know it.
但是我们得继续前进
But we gotta keep going.
好吧
OK.
你能走么?
Can you move your legs?
扶我起来 小子
Just help me up, son.
那些鸽子飞得比你想象的快很多
These doves fly a lot faster than you think.
所以你得努力跟上它们
So you gotta really lead them.
如果你在高处放飞了...
If you have to drop it in high cover...
是的 你打中了
Yeah, you did.
好枪法 儿子
Good shot, son.
John 你母亲...
John your mother...
她可能有点疯
John, your mother,she may be a little crazy,
但是 至少把我们联系到了一起
but at least she brought us together.
感谢上帝这发生在现在
And thank God it happened now,
在我们都还有时间的时候
while we still have time.
我们去找你的鸟吧
Let's find your bird.
她是我奶妈
She was my nanny.
Theresa  她是我奶妈
Theresa, she was my nanny.
我母亲并不是经常在我身边
My mother wasn't around much.
我需要人来照顾我
I needed someone to take it out on.
我的卧室在楼梯的最上面
My bedroom was at the top of a flight of stairs.
并且我会整天坐在床上用对讲机呼叫她
And I would sit in bed all day,calling her on the intercom.
一天她踩空了一脚
One day she took a bad step.
扭了她的脖子
Broke her neck.
我当时6岁
I was six.
有什么这么好笑?
What the hell is so funny?
那是你看见的飞机么?
Is that the plane you saw?
我说的就是它
As best I can tell.
-你真的看见了?  -是的
-You really saw it?  -Yeah.
我真的看见了
I really saw it.
你认为它在这儿多久了?
How long do you think it's been there?
没关系
Doesn't matter.
重要的是我们找到了
What's important is that we found it.
并且重要的是里面有什么
What's important is what's inside it.
里面有什么 John?
What is inside of it John?
这就的需要你爬上去看看了
You're gonna have to climb up there for us and find out.
你还能改变主意
You can still change your mind.
啊  他们已经给我刮过背上的毛了
Nah. They already shaved my back.
我真的很感谢你 John
I'm so thankful for you, John
这是命中注定的
This was meant to be.
回头再见 儿子
See you on the other side, son.
如果你想要大便样本 你还是放弃吧
If you're looking for a stool sample,you can forget it.
自从我们来这个小岛你看了很多书
You've been reading a lot......since we came to the island.
是的 那又怎么样?
OK. So what?
你...
You...
你患了...
You've got...
你得了远视眼
You've got hyperopia.
远视眼?
Hyperopia?
这个那个...
That's...
那是什么?
What is that?
你有远视
You're farsighted.
远视?
Farsighted?
是的 它会在生活中产生 特别是你强加给眼睛压力
Yeah.It can develop later in life when you add a new strain to the eyes.
比如看书
Like with reading.
模糊的
Blurry.
好点还是更糟?
Better or worse?
算了 算了
Uh-uh. No way.
Kate 这不是时装秀
Kate, it's not a fashion show.
哈 哈 很有趣
Har har, very funny.
伙计 像是有人扮成了哈里波特
Dude.Looks like someone steamrolled Harry Potter.
很好笑 是么?
You love this, don't you?
好说好说
You're welcome.
抓住
Hang on.
Boone
我没事
I'm fine.
Boone 你看到什么了?
Boone, what do you see?
Boone
你想知道你该死的飞机里有什么么 Locke?
You wanna know what's in your damn plane?
让你看看
Here's your sign.
他们是走私毒品的 Locke
They're drug smugglers.
海洛因 这就是里面的东西
Heroin. That's all that's in here.
我不懂
I don't understand.
Boone
Boone 出来
Boone, get out!
喂 喂
Hello. Hello.
有人没? 求救 求救
Anybody out there? Mayday! Mayday!
Boone 没时间了 快出来
There's no time. Get out now!
-谁呼叫?  -喂 喂
-Is someone there?  -Hello! Hello!
听得到我么?
Can you hear me?
请重复一遍
Repeat your transmission, please.
听着 我们是海洋航空815航班坠机的幸存者
Hello! We're survivors of the crash of Oceanic flight 815.
-请核查  -快出来
-Please copy.  -Get out now!
815航班没有幸存者
Hello. We're survivors of flight 815.
那么你是什么时候知道他有远视的 在问他最后一次性病发作的时间前还是后?
So did you know before or after you asked him about his latest outbreak?
我不会回答的  Kate
I'd answer that,Kate,
你也知道 医生和病人的对话保密
you know,doctor-patient confidentiality.
当然
Of course.
谢谢你帮他
Thank you for helping him.
我知道这也许是你想做的最后的事了
I know it was probably the last thing you wanted to do.
我不是为了他
I didn't do it for him.
Jack 救命
Jack! Help!
不 不 不 不 把他放在那儿
No, no, no. Put him down up here.
好了 好了 就这里
All right.That's it.
慢点 慢点
OK. Easy. Easy.
出了事故
There was an accident.
Boone从我们追踪的地点附近的悬崖上摔下来了
Boone fell off a cliff out near the place where we were hunting.
好的 我要些水
OK, I'm gonna need some water.
衬衣 毛巾 一切可以止血的东西
Shirts, towels. Anything that I can use to staunch the bleeding.
Kate 快 拜托
Kate, now! Please.
John 详细告诉我发生了什么
John, tell me exactly what happened.
John?
Locke
我这人真是太善良了
I think what you did was so kind.
-我的父亲在哪儿?  -谁?
-Where's my father?  -Who?
我们一起做移植手术的
We had the transplant together.
我不知道他是你的父亲
I didn't know he was your father.
我们的姓不同 但是...
We don't have the same last name.
他在哪儿?
Where is he?
Cooper先生下午付账离开了
Mr. Cooper checked out this afternoon.
他回家了 他有私人看管
He went back home. He's under private care.
那并不代表...什么会...
That doesn't make any...What...
他给我留了口信没?
Did he leave me a message?
不 据我所知事情不是这样
No, not that I know of.
放松一下Locke先生 我给你拿点果汁
You just relax, Mr. Locke.I'm gonna get you some juice.
这是他的主意
It was his idea.
很抱歉 John
I'm sorry, John.
你在这儿干什么?
What are you doing here?
我要点钱
I needed some money.
他总是那么好
He's always been good that way.
你父亲总是很慷慨
Your father's always been generous.
你告诉我我没有父亲
You told me I didn't have a father.
呃 他说这是你会捐肾给他的唯一的方法
He said that was the only way you would give it to him.
这得是你的想法
It had to be your idea.
他告诉我怎么找到你
He told me where to find you.
他叫我去见你
He asked me to go see you.
我想见你
I wanted to see you.
这不可能的
This can't be happening.
这...这是个误会
This is a misunderstanding.
这不会...这不会在我身上发生
This can't happen to me.
他不会这么对我
He wouldn't do this to me.
He wouldn't do this to me!
Eddie  打开门
Eddie, open the gate!
Cooper先生此时不会客
Mr. Cooper's not seeing guests.
我不是客人
I'm not a guest.
抱歉  John
I'm sorry, John.
Eddie  打开门
Eddie, open the gate.
抱歉 我想让你挪一下你的车
I'm sorry. I'm gonna need you to move your car.
我知道你看着我
I know you're watching me.
你不能这么做
You can't do this.
John 拜托 挪下你的车
John, please.Move your car.
我做了你让我做的每件事
I've done everything you wanted me to do.
你为什么还这样对我?
So why did you do this to me?
==============| YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报 ====